很强的爆发力  推进
Good explosion! Drive it!
推进  推进
Drive it! Drive it!
你在观察77号吗
You watching 77?
我在观察所有人
I'm watching everybody.
没必要观察所有人
You don't need to watch everybody.
只要观察77号就行了
You need to watch 77.
你是他的经纪人吗
You're his agent?
我只是一个就事论事的母亲
Just an objective mom.
他的爆发力很强
His explosion is impressive.
他不仅具有很强的爆发力  他还收放自如
It's not just burst. He can pull too.
这是他能进重点中学的原因
You know, the only reason he went to a double "A" School,
不过他有些大器晚成
he was a bit of a late bloomer.
他现在已经成器了
He's a big man now.
你该做他的经纪人
You should be his agent.
好球  77号
Nice pancake, 7-7!
你在选秀榜上的排名提升了
You're moving up those draft boards!
谢谢
Thank you, sir!
突破1号位  预备
On one, on one. Ready?
开始
Break!
蓝队90  冲啊
Blue 90. Hike!
表现的不错  很棒
Good job! Second level, nice!
别挡着我们的四分卫
You off our quarterback!
训练结束  训练结束
Play's over! The play is over!
哨子声后就该停止进攻
Save the aggression for between the whistles!
达里
Daryl.
好了  你们继续训练
All right, back to work!
达里
Daryl.
达里  住手
Daryl, stop!
你在做什么
What are you doing?
你在干嘛
划艇而已
Canoeing.
不过貌似我是在划水
But I seem to be taking on water.
这可不行  用你自己的洗手间去
This is not okay. Use your own bathroom.
我的洗手间没有划艇
No canoe in my bathroom.
我的腿又疼了  泡一泡会舒服些
My leg hurts. Soaking it makes it feel better.
你是这间公寓的主人
You were the one who had to have this condo.
下回你该认真考虑一下房子的基础设施
Maybe next time you should consider amenities,
比如两间包含整套卫浴设备的洗手间
Like two full baths,
而不是仅以和卡迪竞拍为乐
instead of just the joy Of outbidding Cuddy.
掏钱的那个人有权选择卧室
The guy who signs the loan gets to pick the bedrooms.
离我的卧室远点
Stay out of mine.
把手是我安装的  你还欠我35美金
Well, you owe me 35 bucks for the grab rail I installed.
把成人影片关了  老大来了
Hit the kill screen. Boss is here.
这不是色情片  是我们的新病人
It's not porn. It's our new patient.
真失落
Bummer.
男性  22岁  高6尺7寸  310磅
22-year-old male-- 6'7", 310 pounds.
显然脑部有问题
Clearly has brain involvement.
该名男子完全不记得整个事件的经过
The guy has no recollection of this entire incident.
橄榄球运动员
Football player.
这些人的头经常被撞  是吧
Those the ones that get hit in the head a lot, right?
急诊室对他做了CT
E.R. Ct'd him--
结果显示没有脑震荡  也没有中风
no concussion, no stroke,
也没有皮质退化
No cortical degeneration.
同时也对他做了全套心理评估
And he had a full psyche evaluation.
他没疯
He's not crazy.
那就是固醇狂躁咯[类固醇的副作用]
So it's roid rage.
我认为他可不是自然而然就长那么强壮的
I don't think they grow them that big naturally.
急诊室也测试过他体内的类固醇含量
E.R. also tested for steroids.
他没有使用类固醇
He's clean.
这只能说明他搞到的是好东西
Only proving that our guy got his hands on the good stuff.
阴性检测结果至少表明不太可能是类固醇
The negative test at least means steroids is less likely.
我们应该考虑其他的因素
We should discuss other possibilities.
为什么
Why?
每次比赛前他都喷利多卡因
He injects his sore ankles
以缓解脚踝的疼痛
with lidocaine every game.
你觉得他会不使用类固醇吗
You think he's above injecting steroids?
头部频繁受创会损伤脑基底  引发脑垂体瘤
Repeated head trauma could damage the base of the brain,
从而释放GNrH[促性腺激素释放激素]
Leading to a pituitary adenoma, which leaks GNrH.
电脑断层扫描无法检测出脑垂体损伤
Pituitary damage wouldn't be visible on a CT scan.
导致过量分荷尔蒙素从而引起暴躁
Could cause the excess hormones that could cause the rage
这也能躲过急诊室的类固醇检验
And would elude the E.R. steroid test.
好吧
Fine.
采用双侧静脉采样检测GNrH是否升高
Bilateral venous sampling to find the elevated GNrh.
做个核磁共振检查是否有脑垂体损伤
MRI to find the pituitary damage.
如果不是脑垂体损伤
Unless, of course, there is no pituitary damage,
那么他用的的确就是好东西了
in which case, our guy got his hands on the good stuff.
福曼  这些小事你就别操心了
Foreman. Let the peasants handle the peasantry.
你哥哥今天下午要人去接他
Your brother needs to get picked up this afternoon...
他今天出狱
from prison.
你的哥哥  如果你疑惑
Your older brother, in case your confusion is--
你怎么知道的
How do you know about that?
他在电话里留言了
He left a message.
他说他打你和你家里的电话都没人接
Said he couldn't get you on your cell or at home.
我明白  你工作繁忙
I get it. You're busy.
下次他从监狱出来的时候你再去接他吧
You'll pick him up the next time he comes out of prison.
你说完了吗
Is that all?
其实你不忙
You're officially unbusy.
毕竟是一家人
Family is family.
我放你假  去接你哥哥吧
Take the rest of the day. Go see your brother.
我还有工作
I have work to do.
你有没有持续性感觉到隐隐的疼痛呢
Do you feel any pain that's deep and persistent,
还是只有肌肉和关节的疼痛
not just muscles or joints?
我全身一直都疼  这是打橄榄球的原因
Everything hurts all the time. That's football.
这可能不仅仅是打橄榄球的原因
It might not be just football.
我们要检查一下你的脑垂体是否受损
We're gonna test for damage to your pituitary.
如果受损的话  就可能会分泌出过多的荷尔蒙
If there is, it could create excess hormones,
从而引起你的疼痛
which could be causing your pain.
这也就能解释你的暴力行为产生的原因
It would also explain your rage attack.
如果我的脑垂体受损
And if my pituitary is damaged,
要多久才能治好
how long would it take to treat?
我不想妄加揣测
I don't want to get ahead of ourselves
过早预测结果
and start promising deadlines.
不好意思  医生
I-I'm sorry, doctor,
可他这周六得在专业星探
but he's playing in front of pro scouts,
教练还有总经理们面前比赛
coaches, and gms this Saturday.
这是他毕生事业的面试
This is the job interview for the rest of his life.
如果检测结果表明脑垂体受损
If we do find something wrong,
我们可以从鼻腔进入  修复损伤
we can go in through the nose and repair the damage--
不用做大手术
Nothing too invasive.
休息几天就可以恢复
You'll need a couple days of recovery,
到时你就可以及时回到场上比赛了
and then we can have you back by game time.
休息你  医生
Thank you, doctor.
你的眼睛没毛病
There's nothing wrong with your eyes.
是你的工具坏了吧
Well, then your gizmo's broken.
我眼睛发花
I'm seeing spots.
是你得去服役吧
Or you enlisted,
你有着帅气的发型  超赞的牛仔裤
you got the cool haircut and the awesome pants,
可一想到即将奔赴中东服役
then you realized that your plane ticket to the middle east was coach,
然后你就开始反悔了
and you decided to rethink your promise.
不
No.
我已经去过中东了  三次
I've already been there-- three deployments.
现在他们又想让我去
Now they want me to go again.
但我妻子怀孕了
But my wife's pregnant.
你是说你要
So our homeland should be unsafe
舍国家为小家咯
Because your private was unsafe.
我和我妻子都做好完美的计划了
Look, my wife and I planned this perfect.
我的服役本该上周就结束
My enlistment was supposed to be over last week,
所以六个月前她怀孕了
so we got pregnant six months ago.
可他们告诉我我要超期服役
Now they tell me I'm getting stop-lossed--
军队一点都不在乎
Army speak for they don't care about the fact
我的服役已经结束了
that I've already finished my contract.
我才不管他们在不在乎呢
I don't care about the fact that they don't care.
拜托
Hey, come on.
我等了一个多小时才轮到你
I waited an extra hour just to make sure I got you.
为什么
Why?
我看你是瘸子
I saw you limping out there.
越战是吗
Vietnam?
越
Viet--
你以为我多大了
How old do you think I am?
不清楚  越战老士兵的年纪
I don't know, vietnam age?
在那个年代
Well, back in my day,
逃兵们要么躲到加拿大去
the real dodgers had the stones to run up to Canada
要么对自己的脚开一枪
or shoot themselves in the foot.
他们才不会跑到免费诊所来
They didn't come to free clinics
求大夫给开证明呢
whining for doctors' notes.
去抱抱你老婆  让她请个保姆
Go hug your wife. Tell her to get a babysitter.
你会赶回来录下
You'll be back in time to video
你孩子跨出的第一步
the kid's first steps.
不用看扫描结果了
I don't need to see the scan.
你那小狗似的眼神告诉我
I can tell from your little puppy-dog eyes
他的垂体没问题
that his pituitary's fine.
你说  还是我说
Are you gonna say it, or should I?
关于类固醇你说得太对了
You were right about the steroids.
你真是个大天才
You're a genius.
下次说的时候带着感情
Next time with feeling.
给那个骗子注射生长抑素类似物
Put the cheater on a somatostatin analog
清除他体内的类固醇吧
to clear it out of his system.
再让他回到赛场上去
Send him back to his football game.
我从没用过类固醇
I've never done steroids.
你的GnRH高于正常水平
Well, somehow your GnRH got elevated.
这可以让它恢复正常
This will help get it back down.
妈  我发誓
Mom, I swear.
谁还会要你呢  达里
Who's gonna draft you, Daryl?
你都蠢到去用那东西了
You're stupid enough to try that stuff,
何况这周你还要面临测试
especially the week you know you're getting tested.
你们肯定把检查结果弄混了
You guys must've mixed up your labs
会不会是别人的血样  我从来没有
or got somebody else's blood, because I never--
怎么了
Okay, what is that?
心动过速  躺下来  达里
Tachycardia. Lay back down, Daryl.
我的心脏怎么会跳成这样
Why's my heart beating like this?
说明不是类固醇
It's not steroids.
我需要腺苷
I need some adenosine!
把急救车推过来
And get that crash cart over here!
豪斯  下次
House, next time--
马克斯
Marcus.
对了  你们互相认识
Oh, right. You two know each other.
你在这干嘛呢
What are you doing here?
正在面试
Uh, interviewing.
开什么玩笑
Oh! Who are we kidding?
面试结束了  这工作是你的了
Interview's over. You got the job.
什么工作
What job?
我的新助手
My new assistant.
他假释的一部分  他需要一份工作
Part of his parole-- he needs a job.
我尽一份力罢了
Just trying to do my part.
关于类固醇  你错了
You were wrong about the steroids.
病人有阵发性心动过速
Patient had a paroxysmal tachycardia.
我们已经恢复了他的窦性心率
We cardioverted him back to sinus rhythm.
我们会给他做个心电图和甲氧乙腈扫描
We're gonna get an EKG and a sestamibi scan.
马克斯
Marcus
咱们出去谈
Let's talk outside.
毕竟是一家人
Family is family.
我也很高兴见到你
Hey. Good to see you too.
你过得怎么样
Did you have a hard stretch?
还行  就是差点被强奸了
No, not bad. I hardly got raped at all.
你不能在这工作
You can't work here.
你老板说我可以
Well, your boss says I can.
-我不是在开玩笑  -别生气
- I'm not playing. - Lighten up.
会很好玩的
Man, this could be fun.
我可以看看你的生活
I get to see your world.
你可以帮我从药房弄点药
You get me access to the pharmacy.
开玩笑的  拜托
I am playing. Come on, man.
你看上去挺不错的
You look good.
如果你时不时来看看我
I'd already know that if you came to visit
我可能早就知道你过得不错了
every once in a while,
不过没关系  我明白
but whatever, I get it.
你不想见到我
It--it's cool. You don't want to see me.
也不想来接我出狱
You don't want to pick me up.
这些你都有理
It's all justified.
我只是需要重新获得你的信任
I'll just have to win you back over.
让我来澄清一下
Let me explain something.
这个给你工作的人
This man who's offering you the job--
他可不是慈善家
He's not a philanthropist.
他看上去比你热情多了
He seems more helpful than you.
他才不是想帮你
He doesn't want to help you.
只是想利用你来整我罢了
He only wants to use you to screw with me.
你知道最好的反击是什么吗
You know how you can screw with him?
表现出一副你不在乎我在这儿工作的样子
Act like your brother getting a job doesn't screw with you.
相信我吧  如果你告诉他
Trust me, it'll be better for both of us
你不接受这份工作的话
if you go back in there and tell him
对我俩都有好处
you can't take the job.
我可没有资格随便拒绝
I'm not a person who has the luxury
一份工作
of turning down jobs.
找点别的事做
Well, figure something out...
你不能在这工作
'cause you cannot work here.
豪斯
House!
我们花了一整晚  用尽各种仪器
we spent all night, used all the fancy machines.
病人的心脏没有任何问题
Patient's heart looks fine.
如果没有问题
well, if it was fine,
为什么你走进他的病房
It wouldn't go aflutter
他的心就开始嘣蹦乱跳呢
just 'cause you walked into the room.
淡奶油  多加了两份咖啡
Light whip, two extra shots.
谢谢
Thank you, sir.
看你的表情
Judging by the look on your face,
估计你哥哥没听取你的意见辞职
I assume you're upset that big bro didn't
让你很失望
take your advice and skip town.
你把我们的谈话内容告诉他了吗
You told him about our conversation?
他给我买了早餐
He bought me breakfast.
真有趣啊
it was fun.
订一下午餐吧  就你和我
Put lunch in the books, just you and me.
我们的病人有可能是卵园孔未闭
Our patient could have a pfo.
那么自然的你会转到泌尿系统的方向
Well, naturally, you jump right to a urinary issue.
卵圆孔未闭不是泌尿系统问题  是心脏问题
Pfo's not urinary. It's a heart issue.
是吗  哦
It is? Oh.
很自然地  你认为
Well, naturally, you think
不是泌尿系统问题
It's not a urinary issue,
因为你正为你自己
'cause you're so embarrassed about your own
过去的泌尿系统的问题而困扰
Past urinary issues,
你不敢讨论这个问题
You don't dare broach the subject.
别这样
Oh, come on.
你在波比·萨姆森家待了一整晚
You spending the night over at Bobby Samson's.
我没有尿床
I did not wet the bed.
我只是把饮料弄洒了
I spilled a drink.
我们没买饮料吧  埃里克
We're not buying it, Eric.
我们从来没买过
We never bought it.
你干嘛告诉他这些事
Why aryou telling him these things?
有什么大不了的  已经过去25年了
What's the big deal? It was 25 years ago.
充满氧气的和脱氧的血液混合在一起
Oxygenated and deoxygenated blood mix,
快速血流造成了血栓  解释了心脏和头的问题
The rough flow causes a clot, explains the heart and head.
就像洛约拉玛莉曼特大学的那个大前锋
like that power forward from Loyola Marymount,
他  呃...
When he, um...
汉克·盖瑟斯吗  他们情况不一样
Hank Gathers? That's not what happened to him.
让你哥哥说完
Whoa, whoa, whoa, let your brother speak.
头号主将盖瑟斯怎么了
What happened to Hank Gathers?
联盟锦标赛的时候
conference tournament--
空中传球扣篮  把球阻断在主半场
Alley-oop dunk, jams it home.
然后他跑遍全场去拦截
Then he runs up the court and splat.
后来就因心脏病突发就死在
He dropped dead of a heart thing
球场上
Right there on the court.
我记起来了
I remember that.
验尸的时候  他们发现
On autopsy, they found he had
他有心肌肥大症
A hypertrophic cardiomyopathy.
情绪激动心动过速
rage and tachycardia
都是警告
Are warning signs.
你是认真的吗
Seriously?
就因为我哥哥想起了一场篮球赛吗
Because my brother remembers a basketball game?
我不管这些想法是从何而来
Hey, I don't care where an idea comes from,
只要讲得通而且还能让某人尴尬就行
As long as it makes sense and embarrasses someone.
你是不是疯了啊
Are you out of your mind?
作为一个曾经的精神病患者
As a former psychiatric patient,
我拒绝使用这个说法
I take offense at that terminology.
我只不过是想把你赶出我的浴缸而已
All I did was ban you from my tub.
你就用那种方式来给我反馈吗
Whatever happened to proportional response?
那种方式与我们的谈话有什么关联吗
Whatever happened to coherent conversation?
那个...东东...
That...Thing...
打破了瓷砖  刮破了墙壁
Broke tiles, gashed the walls,
还到处大小便
And pooped everywhere.
我开了个修理费的账单...
Expect a bill for repairs...
你来付钱
And payback.
到底怎么了
What was that?
我不知道啊
I have no idea.
大家都认为
Everybody else thinks
是心肌肥大症吗
Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy makes sense?
那后  让病人用跑步机
Good. Stick the patient on a treadmill.
给他的心脏施压直到它停止跳动
Stress his heart until it stops.
你想诱导心搏停止吗
You want to induce cardiac arrest?
唯一对病人用作用的治疗
Only real treatment is for the patient
就是再也不要给他的心脏负担了
Never to stress his heart again,
也就是说我们要告诉他
Which means we have to tell him to retire
在他这个21岁的年龄时该退役了
At the ripe old age of 21.
让他心脏的跳动声比说话声都小
Stopping his heart speaks louder than words.
去吧
Go.
也许这是件好事
Maybe it's a good thing.
他给你哥哥一份工作  一份责任
He gave your brother a job, responsibility.
我不是说他不该工作
I'm not arguing that he shouldn't have a job.
我就是不想他在我们那里工作
I just don't want him having one here.
我理解豪斯这么做是想烦你
I understand that House did this to annoy you.
但他为什么能得逞呢
But why is he succeeding?
你知道我哥哥过去做了些什么
you know what my brother did
上次他出狱之后
The last time he got out of prison?
他偷我爸妈的钱去买毒品
He stole money from my parents to buy drugs.
他抢劫了一家买酒的商店
He robbed a liquor store.
然后去买豪华车
Then he moved on to jacking luxury cars--
上一次
Last time.
每一次
Every time.
我了解他30多年了
I've known my brother for over 30 years.
你一天也没接触过他
You haven't even known him a day.
对不起
I'm sorry.
害虫驱除剂要用250美金
The exterminator charged $250
能够把负鼠赶走
To get the opossum out of there,
承包商估计
And the contractor estimates
要用1500美金修理浴室
$1,500 to fix the bathroom.
你为什么要戏弄福曼
And why are you jerking foreman around?
因为那很有意思
Because it's fun.
或许你让那个
Maybe you should give those bills to the guy
把自己浴室窗户开着的家伙付账单
Who left his own bathroom window open.
你的动机总要比简单的玩笑更深一层
Your motives always run deeper than simple fun.
我想知道更多
I want to learn more
关于我的员工  这样我就能操控他
About one of my employees so that I can manipulate him
然后在需要的时候收拾他一顿
And destroy him if and when I choose.
信息就是力量
Information is power.
-我不信  -好吧
- Not buying it. - Okay.
你为什么不告诉我我的真正险恶的计划呢
Why don't you tell me my real evil plan?
我不觉得有什么险恶的计划
I don't think there is an evil plan.
你觉得你和你的家庭
You regret not having a relationship
没有良好的关系  觉得很遗憾
With your own family,
你不想看到福曼走你的老路
And you don't want to see foreman go down that same path.
我觉得...
I think...
你其实是个好人
You're actually being nice.
闭嘴吧
Oh, shut up.
你不能因为负鼠的事怪罪于我
You can't accuse me of an opossum attack
也不要以为我其实是个好人
And underhanded kindness in the same visit.
我会回来的
Then i'll come back.
跑步机检查做不了了
Treadmill test was a bust.
那个家伙有不可思议的情况
The guy's in unbelievable shape.
我们不能使他的心率达到150
We couldn't get his heart rate above 150.
你们老板其实是个很好的人
Your boss is secretly a very nice man.
我知道啊
I know.
如果我们引发重造心脏病的情况
If we can't re-create the cardiac event,
我们就没办法证明是心肌肥大症
We can't prove Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy.
或者我们找个更大的跑步机...
Either we find a bigger treadmill...
或者...
Or...
难道我没收到你可以自由活动的留言吗
Did I miss the memo about you being released?
我感觉很好
I'm feeling fine.
我不能就这样躺在这儿错过训练
I can't keep laying here in this bed missing practices.
说的太在点了  手臂给我
All excellent points. give me your arm.
你要给我打什么
What's in the shot?
血管扩张剂
It's a vasodilator.
既然跑步机锻炼不了你儿子的心脏
Since we can't exercise your son's heart on the treadmill,
就只好采取化学方法了
I'm gonna have to do it chemically.
怎么了
What's wrong?
你在变白
You're turning white.
这代表什么
What does that mean?
代表他再也不需要
It means he doesn't need football
借橄榄球找工作了
to get a good job anymore.
是雷诺氏现象
Raynaud's phenomenon--
血管痉挛阻断
Vasospasms cut off the blood supply
手指的血液供应
to his fingers.
有可能是风湿性关节炎的早期病征
Could be early onset rheumatoid arthritis.
类风湿因子呈阴性
Rheumatoid factor is negative.
动脉斑块引起的血栓
Arterial plaque throwing clots
可以解释手指  脑部和心脏问题
would explain the fingers, head, heart.
你真的觉得一个血管窄化的人
You really think a guy with stenosis
能撑过平板测验吗
could've aced that treadmill test?
开玩笑吧  你竟然给他弄了张桌子
You're kidding me. You got him a desk?
还有名牌呢
And a nameplate.
男人需要有自己的地盘
Man's got to have a place he can call his own.
会不会是多发性大动脉炎
What about Takayasu's Arteritis?
淋巴瘤更符合  得摘掉他的脾
Lymphoma's a better fit. We should remove his spleen.
直接跳到手术环节太鲁莽了
Bold move to skip straight to surgery.
他的重要赛事快到了
His big game's coming up.
没时间在那儿做做活检
We don't have time to biopsy,
等等报告  再做做手术
wait for the pathology report, and resect.
太对了
Right.
我们应该一点根据都没有地切了他的脾
We should remove his spleen without confirmation
好让他赶上他那重要赛事
so he won't miss the big game.
滴注乙醇
Hang an ethanol drip.
那既不治淋巴瘤也不治
That won't treat
多发性大动脉炎
for either lymphoma or takayasu's.
如果是淋巴瘤他就会发痒
If it's lymphoma, the ethanol will make him itchy,
福曼就能去切他的脾
And foreman can remove his spleen.
如果是大动脉炎  桡动脉就会没脉搏
If it's Takayasu's, he'll lose his radial pulse,
奇斯就能用他的类固醇了
And Chase can start him on steroids.
马克斯
Marcus!
你在这儿干嘛
What are you doing here?
新任务是在敌国领土上
My new assignment is to shadow you
盯你们的梢
in enemy territory
记录你们对病人说的每一个字
And document your every word to the patient.
别说傻话
Just don't say anything stupid.
你不是白痴  别这么做
You're not an idiot. Don't do this.
拜托  兄弟
Come on, man.
我改过自新了
I'm a new person now--
不再吸毒  不再撒谎
no more drugs, no more lying.
要是连我家人都不给我
And if i can't get my own family
一个机会来证明
to give me an opportunity to prove that,
这又有什么意义呢
Then what's the point?
爸妈给过你机会
Mom and dad gave you a chance
一而再
and a second
再而三
and a third.
我不会再纵容你了
I'm not about to give you a 54th.
你家奴才怎么没来接你吃午饭呢
Why isn't your minion fetching your lunch?
正忙着暗中监视他的弟弟呢
He's busy spying on his little brother.
什么
What?
这可挺伤自尊的啊
That's very demeaning.
显然你又要发表
You obviously have a theory
伤人自尊之不为伤人自尊的理论了
as to why demeaning is not demeaning.
你在变本加厉
You're escalating
想证明你不像我想的那样在做好人
to prove I was wrong about you being nice,
只有我说对了你才会这么做
Which you would only do if i was right.
你听过自己在说些什么吗
Do you even listen to yourself?
急诊室刚来了一个23岁病人
23-year-old just came into the E.R.,
指明要点你
asked for you.
她罩杯多大
What's her cup size?
我不认为他的罩杯
I don't think his cup size
和他的状况有关系
is relevant to his condition.
他不小心往自己脚开了一枪
He accidentally shot himself in the foot.
说真的吗
Seriously?
我让你在移民加拿大和
I give you a choice between moving to Canada
给自己的脚打一枪中间选
and shooting yourself in the foot,
你竟然选了后者吗
And you chose the bullet?
我不想当逃兵
I didn't want to be a fugitive.
你以为这就能让你退伍了吗
You think this is gonna get you discharged?
我们会给你缝好针然后直接送你回去
We'll patch it up and send you right back.
别帮我治疗
Don't patch it up.
听着
Look...
你被自己的政府搞得一团糟
You got screwed over by your own government,
那真的很恶心
And that sucks.
但你这样做只能得到
But all you're gonna get out of this
五天的假和一片创可贴
Is a five-day vacation and a band-aid.
当初签合同的时候  我只是个男孩子
When i signed up, I was just a guy.
现在我要做爸爸了
Now I'm about to be a dad.
要是回去那儿
I go back over,
我的孩子很有可能会没有父亲
there's a chance my kid grows up without a father.
即使搞大了一个女孩的肚子
You got a girl pregnant.
你也还只是一个男孩
You're still just a guy.
我们得等多久
How much longer we have to wait?
一直到你
We have to keep going
有些感觉为止
until you start feeling something.
要是你说出我该感觉到什么
Might help if, uh, you told me
应该会比较有帮助
what I'm supposed to feel.
要是我说了  你就会满脑子想着
If i do that, that's all you'll be thinking about.
这样你告诉我的就不是你真正的感觉了
then you'll be telling me that's what you're feeling--
暗示的力量
Power of suggestion.
之前另一个黑人的伙计也在这儿
The other black dude who was in here earlier,
你兄弟吗
He your brother?
谁告诉你的
What gave it away?
你看他的表情
The way you looked at him.
我有两个哥哥
I have two older brothers,
我们总想把对方杀掉
and we always want to kill each other.
有什么问题么
Something wrong?
还好
Not really.
只是有点痒
It just feels itchy.
你等的就是这个吗
Is that what you're waiting for?
说明更有可能是淋巴瘤
Means lymphoma's most likely,
但这是好消息
but that's actually good news.
怎么会是好消息呢
How could that be good news?
那是能治愈的
Because it's treatable.
今晚我们就能用腹腔镜切除你的脾
We can remove your spleen tonight laparoscopically.
周六我能跑动了吗
Will I be able to run by saturday?
可以在闲季的时候再做放疗
We can get to the radiation in the off-season.
嘿  妈
Hey, ma.
妈  醒醒  快醒醒
Wake up, ma. Wake up.
我开始发痒了  也就是说我快能打球了
I'm itchy. Means I can play.
你黑灯瞎火地干嘛呢
What are you doing in the dark?
躺着等你
Lying in wait.
天呐  你的脸怎么了
Jeez. What happened to your face?
很好  装无辜这招
Right... play innocent.
难道不是你想要为了那个玩笑
Like you weren't looking for revenge for the prank
报复我吗
that I didn't pull.
你这是因果报应  但不是我干的
It's karmic justice, but I didn't do it.
睁着眼睛说瞎话  你挑起了战争
Of course you realize, this means war.
隔开胃网膜动脉
Isolating the gastroepiploic artery.
接近了
Nearly there.
福曼  过来看这个
Foreman, come and take a look at this.
他的肝脏发炎了
Liver's inflamed.
那么发痒不是脾的原因
So the itching wasn't caused by his spleen.
也就不是淋巴瘤
It's not lymphoma.
你的脸怎么了
What happened to your face?
威尔森侵略了苏台德区[希特勒侵略捷克的第一步]
Wilson annexed the Sudetenland.
T细胞和B细胞无异常
No abnormal "t" cells or "b" cells.
可以肯定不是淋巴瘤
It's definitely not lymphoma.
肝脏活体检查只显示有
Liver biopsy only revealed
一般炎症
nonspecific inflammation.
是不是你壮着胆子
Kind of like the time you took
吃了你妈妈的避孕药
your mom's birth control pills
结果却搞得自己乳头肿胀
on a dare and ended up with swollen nipples.
我没干过
That never happened.
是啊  还有你在高中的昵称
Right, and your nickname
从没叫过艾丽卡
all the way up through high school wasn't Erica.
没有的事
It wasn't.
好吧  这是我编的
Okay, I may have made that one up,
我本来觉得我弟弟
with the understanding that my brother
还有些幽默感
still had a sense of humor
能一起开开玩笑的
and would figure out to play along.
多发性肌炎可以解释
Polymyositis would explain
头部  肝脏  心脏
the head, liver, heart,
-甚至是手指发白的问题  -还有
- even the white fingers. - It would also be accompanied
肌肉无力并发症
by a significant decrease in muscle power.
马克斯
Marcus!
给你个实践机会
Chance to redeem yourself.
对你来说我们的病人够壮吗
Does our patient look strong to you?
抱歉  艾瑞克
Sorry, Eric.
你哥哥不认同你的诊断
Big brother disagrees with your diagnosis.
费尔蒂综合征
Felty syndrome?
你自己说过发炎的是肝不是脾
You said the liver was inflamed, not the spleen.
真不敢相信这家伙是做手术的
Can you believe they let this guy perform surgery?
-你干嘛呢  -请求一个许可
- What are you doing? - Requesting permission
让我阐述意见的时候
to share my idea without being belittled
不在你的新助理面前丢脸
in front of your new assistant.
请求驳回  继续
Permission denied. Continue.
病人两个踝关节都有软组织损伤
Our patient has cartilage damage in both ankles.
他在每场比赛前都会注射利多卡因
He gets lidocaine shots before every game
来麻醉  减轻疼痛
to mask the pain.
队医不小心把一个针头重复用了两次
Team doctor uses the same needle twice by accident.
是病毒性肝炎
Viral hepatitis.
你觉得他是白痴吗  马克斯
You think he's an idiot, Marcus?
-我不觉得他是  -好的
- I don't think he's an idiot. - Okay.
去给他验血
Go test his blood.
走吧  我们该吃午餐了
Come on. We have a lunch scheduled.
你把我忽悠了
So you jerked me around.
其实你站在你弟弟的阵营
Your allegiance lies with your brother.
我终于知道了  你真厉害
I get it. Admirable.
但问题在于
Here's the problem.
我是为了你告诉我实话才雇你的
I hired you to tell me the truth.
你要是不能实话实说  你就失业了
If you don't do that, you no longer have a job.
我不明白你到底想要知道什么
I don't know what secret you're looking to uncover,
但我弟弟是个正直的人
but my brother is a decent guy.
他因为偷车被捕过
He was arrested for grand theft auto.
你要失望了
You're gonna be disappointed.
你说说看
Try me.
我告诉你我那时和他一起了吗
He tell you I was with him?
是你出的主意
Was it your idea?
我们干什么都一起
We did everything together.
我忘了是谁的主意了
I don't know whose idea it was.
我那时16岁  他才14岁
I was 16. he was only 14.
我们这种小混混连方向盘都碰不到
Little punk couldn't even see over the steering wheel.
他用一把螺丝刀开得
He's quicker with a flathead screwdriver
比一般人用钥匙都快
than most people with a key.
抱歉因为无聊的医疗破事
Sorry to interrupt my character assassination
打断了你们对我的名誉陷害
with boring medical stuff,
但我们给病人抽血时
but when we drew the patient's blood,
血在采血管里就凝结了
it clotted right there in the vacutainer.
那就是说问题不在他血液里的东西
So the problem is not in his blood,
而是他的血液本身
it's the blood itself.
他每周两次在寒冷的户外锻炼
He's been working out in the cold doing two-a-days.
所以得了冷凝球蛋白血症
It's got to be cryoglobulinemia.
我喜欢震惊的坏消息
I usually love breaking bad news.
但这个就...
But in this case...
给病人用华法林[抗凝血药]
Start the patient on warfarin.
抱歉中途打断了  你刚才说...
I'm so sorry about that. You were saying...
我们只开了10分钟就被捕了
We drove for about ten minutes before we got caught,
就是这样
and that was it.
我们的妈妈来到警察局
When our mom came down to the station,
再把我们带回家  一路上一语不发
she didn't say a word the whole ride home.
她把车开上车道  熄火
She came up to the driveway, turned off the car.
我们沉默地坐着
We're sitting in there in silence.
然后她没有转身  说道
Then without turning around, she said,
"我会为你们祈祷的"
"I'll pray for you."
再后来她下了车
And she got out of the car.
你们的处罚倒是不重
You got off easy.
对你我来说不重
Easy for you, easy for me,
但对他来说不是
Not easy for Eric.
从那时起  他的人生目标就是
His life mission became to never disappoint
再也不让妈妈对他失望
our mother like that again,
因为他是个好人
because he is a good guy.
我原以为他的悼词上会有这个故事
I thought he would tell that story at the eulogy.
但却没有
But I heard he didn't give one.
你们的...
Your...
你们的母亲去世了
your mother's dead?
要是他告诉你  我想他是有原因的
If he didn't tell you, I'm sure he had a reason.
听着  你尽可以随意愚弄他
Look, you can mock him all you want
嘲笑他尿床什么的
about peeing in the bed,
但请你...
Please...
请你别提我们的母亲
Don't bring up our mother.
你的血液里含有多的离谱的一种
Your blood contains an abnormally high volume
叫冷凝球蛋白的蛋白质
of certain proteins called cryoglobulins.
它们遇冷变稠
They become thick when it gets cold outside.
这就像车子跑过一段时间后
It's like a car trying to run
汽油变成油渣一样
after the oil's turned to sludge.
我们认为这才是真正的元凶
We think that's what's been causing all your problems.
那么我只需要换点润滑油
So I just need a quick oil change
就又能横冲直撞了吗
And I'm good to go.
换润滑油可没那么容易
This oil change isn't so quick.
我们得给你用血液稀释剂
We have to put you on blood thinners
和其他的药物
And other medications.
一个疗程需要两到三周
The process will take two to three weeks.
但是以后
But after that,
你就能毫无障碍的打球了
You should be able to play without a problem.
以后就没事了
After that, it's not gonna matter.
医生  如果达里在周六的比赛中没有好表现
Doctor, if Daryl doesn't play in front of the scouts
他就不能被球探选中选秀
On saturday, he won't get drafted.
不能推迟到比赛后吗
Can't you wait until after the game?
如果我们推迟治疗
If we wait and let him play,
他很有可能
There's a good chance he dies
猝死在赛场上
Right on the field.
上帝显灵了
I had an epiphany.
那一般意味着你又要赢了
Usually that precedes you walking away with purpose, so...
一字花螺丝刀
Flathead screwdriver.
我应该说什么呢
And then I say...?
这不是游戏
It's not a game.
这证明不是你拆掉扶杆
It's proof that you didn't rig the grab rail
让我摔倒
And make me fall.
我已经有充分的证据证明
I already have proof of that--
那不是我干的了
The fact that I didn't do it.
我不信
I can't go on that.
但是我相信
But I can go on the fact
我不得不从诺拉手里借一字换螺丝刀
That I had to borrow a flathead screwdriver from Nora
来装东西  因为我们只有个十字花的
To install the thing, 'cause we only had a phillips-head.
然后  那天晚上晚些时候去还的时候
And then, of course, I returned it late that night
一不小心
In a completely successful effort
看到她没穿胸罩的样子
To see her braless...
等下  等下
Whoa. wait. wait a minute. wait a minute.
这意味你没有使用螺丝刀
Which means that you didn't have the tool to sabotage
破坏扶杆
The grab rail.
只穿了毛衣
Braless under, like, a sweater
或是其他的
Or, like, a--like, a--
现在我同样有证据证明
Now I also have proof
臭鼬事件不是我的责任
That i'm not responsible for the opossum,
因为我减轻了你的责任
Because I'm absolving you
而不是增重你的负担
Of responsibility instead of escalating,
你知道的  不像我的风格
Which you know is not my nature.
那么是有人闯进咱们的房子
So someone is breaking into our place
只是为了挑拨咱俩的关系
Just to screw with us?
臭鼬
The opossum...
是为我准备的
Was meant for me.
我太累了
I'm so tired.
以前到半夜2点都很兴奋
It was exciting till about 2:00 A.M.
而现在只是一种折磨
Now it's just torture.
你没上过大学吗
Did you even go to college?
这就是增重我的负担
This is the escalation, isn't it?
熬夜到天明  然后无事发生
Keeping me up all night, nothing happens,
然后明天又要熬夜到天明
Then you keep me up all night again tomorrow.
这就是你的报复
This is your retaliation.
你看  这是不符合逻辑的
You see, that's just illogical,
因为我也在熬夜
'cause I'm staying up too.
也许你整天打盹呢
Maybe you napped all day.
我以经验主义为证证明我没有玩弄你
I gave you empirical proof that I did not prank you.
不  你没有
No. No, you did not.
你创造了一种经验主义并以它为证
You created empirical proof that I didn't prank you,
鼓吹一种概念证明你没有玩弄我
Selling me on the notion that you didn't prank me.
有可能是自我玩弄
Maybe you self-pranked.
我从不自我玩弄
I don't master-prank.
那个削去面颊的事是真的吗
Is that cut on your cheek even real?
看见了吗  这正是我们的敌人所希望的
See, this is exactly what our nemesis wants--
各个击破
Divide and conquer.
-你还没看出来吗  -好吧
- Can't you see that? - Okay.
我要去睡觉了
I'm going to bed.
我告诉你  要是你现在去睡觉
I'm telling you, if you sleep now,
醒来你的枕边就会放着个死马头
You're gonna wake up next to severed horse heads.
或者更糟  无头马
Or worse, the rest of it.
豪斯
House!
平板电视
The flat screen!
你绝对不会牺牲平板电视的
You would never sacrifice the flat screen.
这小子太赞了
Oh, this guy is good.
这样做有理由吗
is there a reason for this?
当然有充分理由
there is a reason
解释这一切  我的朋友们
For everything, mes amis.
我不得不说我们中间隐藏着
I am troubled to report that we have
一个罪犯
A criminal in our midst.
犯什么罪了
Guilty of what exactly?
昨晚  防火喷头把我们的房子给淹了
Last night, the fire sprinklers flooded our apartment.
在那之前
And before that,
我在我的浴缸里发现了一只臭鼬
I found an opossum in my bathtub.
你们每个人都有作案动机
You each had motive.
都有作案机会
You each had opportunity.
这就是你说的紧急事件吗
This is the emergency you paged me about?
别激动
Not so fast,
卡迪小姐
Mademoiselle Cuddy.
在你们交代清楚
No one leaves here
昨晚的去向之前
Until they can account for their whereabouts
谁也不准离开
The evening last.
再见
Bye.
好吧
okay, no one
我雇佣的人
Who is employed by me leaves here
在交代清楚昨晚的去向前不准离开
Until they account for their whereabouts the evening last.
从你开始怎么样  奇斯医师
What about you, professor Chase?
为什么是我
Why would I?
因为你一直认为我是
Because you hold me responsible for
导致你婚姻破裂的人
Breaking up your marriage.
我和十三一直在这
I was here all night with thirteen,
观察病人静脉注射血液稀释剂
Monitoring our patient's I.V. Blood thinners.
你们谁能证明
Can either of you prove that?
病人还活着并且有病情在好转
The patient's alive and improving.
这还不够吗
Is that proof enough?
暂时可以  你呢  陶博上校
For now. What about you, colonel Taub?
我和我太太出去吃晚饭了
I was out to dinner with my wife.
真的吗
Really?
是你太太
Your wife.
是的  真的
Yes, really.
很好
Good enough.
因为我一直打压你
'cause I had you pegged all along.
你当然最有嫌疑
You certainly had all the motive in the world.
首先
First of all,
我不感兴趣
I'm not interested.
其次  我不知道你们住在 哪
Second, I don't even know where you guys live.
昨天我刚证明你是个骗子
Yesterday I confirmed that you are a liar.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
至少是省略细节的撒谎者
Well, at least a liar by omission.
豪斯
House!
别说
Don't.
听好了  同学们
Get this, class.
福曼的妈妈去世了
Foreman's mom died.
他有告诉过你们吗
He ever tell any of you?
豪斯
House,
我觉得你跑题了
I think you're getting off topic here.
他说真的吗
Is he serious?
你的妈妈去世了吗
Did your mom pass away?
三个月之前
About three months ago.
我真的很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
你为什么不告诉我们呢
Why didn't you tell anybody?
更糟糕的是
And to top it off,
你拒绝在葬礼上为她美言几句
You refused to say anything nice about her at the funeral.
我不说是因为那跟别人无关
I didn't talk because it isn't anyone's business.
别说了
Stop.
你不需要向这个人解释什么
You don't have to explain yourself to this guy.
你想打我  对吧
You want to hit me, don't you?
马克斯  住手
Marcus, don't.
我不干了
I quit.
你应该去阻止他  他需要这份工作
You should stop him. He needs this job.
我们的病人需要再来一次静脉注射
Our patient needs a fresh I.V.
我不需要两个或是三个星期
I don't need two or three weeks.
看到了吗  我的颜色恢复了
See? Got my color back.
只能说明你在恢复
That means you're getting better.
-但不能说明  -说明我好了
- But it doesn't mean - It means I am better.
我的教练让球队医生来看过了
My coach had the team doctor come by.
他认为我可以打球了
He cleared me to play.
你的球队医生有没有意识到你在使用血液化稠剂呢
Did your team doctor realize you're on blood thinners?
我现在没有用了
I'm off them now.
你还是很虚弱
You're still sick.
你还不能停止治疗
You're not ready to go off your meds.
达里  听他的  不值得冒险
Daryl, listen to him. It is not worth the risk.
我星期天会回来的  妈妈
I'll come back on Sunday, mom.
到那时只要病情需要  你们随便开药
You guys can give me all the meds I need then.
这样的治疗方式不合适
The treatment doesn't work that way.
请跟着他吧
Please go with him.
抗生素不起作用
Antibiotics aren't working.
我们准备给你换不同的
We're gonna switch you to different ones,
不过你将失去你的指头了
But you're gonna lose your toe.
太好了  战士
Outstanding, soldier.
一般来说
As a general rule,
在你庆贺之前  先做一点研究
Before you celebrate, do a little research.
军队医疗检测协会
The army's medical evaluation board
绝对会容许
Is perfectly fine
一个只有九个脚趾的步兵通过
With nine-toed infantrymen,
只要他们还能走路和跑步
As long as they can walk and run.
所以我丢了一个指头却一无所获
So I lost a toe for nothing?
恐怕是这样
Afraid so.
除非你想让我继续给你使用旧的抗生素
Unless you want me to keep you on the old antibiotics,
让感染范围扩大
Let the infection spread,
这样我们就不止切除一个指头了
And we could amputate more than just a toe.
为什么你为了这个甘愿冒生命危险
Why are you risking your life for this?
你妈妈并不想你去
Your mom doesn't want you to.
我的妈妈为我牺牲了一切
My mom sacrificed everything for me.
她告诉我不要来
Her telling me not to come here
恰恰是另一个证明
is just another example of that.
如果我做得好  我就能照顾
I do good out there, I could take care of her
她的余生
for the rest of her life.
如果我不为她做出牺牲  我算什么
Who am I if I don't sacrifice for her?
这才是一家人
That's family.
你还好吧
You okay?
所有东西都很模糊
Everything's blurry.
我什么都看不见了
I can't see.
带我回医院吧
Take me back to the hospital.
失明说明我们对他估计错误
The blindness means we were wrong about his--
事实上  我有责任
Actually, I'm responsible for that.
偷偷在他的水瓶里加上硝酸盐
Spiked his water bottle with nitrates,
使他的血压下降
dropped his blood pressure,
夺走了他脑部的多氧血液
robbed oxygen-rich blood from his brain,
让他失明
Making him blind.
一个暂时失明的病人
Figured a temporarily blind patient
比一个永久性死亡的病人好处理
is better than a permanently dead one.
我把他送回医院的时候
Vision was already coming back
他的视力已经恢复了
by the time I dropped him off at the hospital.
干得好
Well played.
真希望你的医疗小把戏能
If only we could combine your medical chicanery
和你兄弟给我取摩卡咖啡的本领结合起来
with your brother's ability to fetch me mochas,
这样你就是个完美的福曼了
You'd be the perfect foreman.
你在哪里
Where are you?
我在忙
I'm busy.
很好  这样一来我们就没有新症状
Great. So we don't have a new symptom.
也就是说我们必须让他继续使用血液化稠剂
Means we should just stick him back on his blood thinners,
这样他过几周就能康复了
and he should be okay to leave in a couple weeks.
事实上  确实出现了一个新症状
Actually, we do have a new symptom.
你们没人看他的重新接纳图吗
Any of you take a look at his readmittance chart?
在他刚来的时候
Between the time he checked in
和他再一次报道的时候
and the time he rechecked in,
我们的病人瘦了一磅
Our patient lost a single pound.
一个那样的病人通常会减十磅
Patient like that would usually shed over ten pounds.
最直接的答案应该是类固醇
The obvious answer would be steroids,
但是我们已经排除了
But since we've already ruled them out...
所以他没有注射过
So he's not injecting.
但是有可能自然获得
But he could be getting them naturally--
类肿瘤性症状
Paraneoplastic syndrome.
身体产生抗生素  与癌抗衡
The body produces antibodies, which battle cancer,
看起来也像荷尔蒙增长
which could also act like growth hormone.
我们已经排除了淋巴瘤
We've eliminated lymphoma.
有什么其他癌类似于荷尔蒙增长呢
What other cancers mimic growth hormone?
肺  胰腺  肾脏  胸部
Lung, pancreatic, renal, breast--
这是反问句  我不在意
It was a rhetorical question. I don't really care.
把每个部分都检查一遍
Go test him for all of them.
你来这干什么
What are you doing here?
你需要一份工作
You need a job.
也许我可以再跟豪斯谈谈
Maybe I can talk to House,
看是否能要回你的工作
see if I can get your job back.
一旦他知道你跟我和好了
Soon as he knows you're okay with me being there,
他就不会再让我回去了
he won't want me back.
也许我能帮你找到别的工作
Maybe I can help you figure out something else.
我保证
I promise...
我不会再让你失望了
I won't let you down.
别说这个
Don't do that.
我们就
Let's just...
顺其自然
See how it goes.
他们有规定你
So, uh, do they mandate you
必须住在这个过渡教习所
to stay here at the halfway house?
还是你可以跟家里人一起住呢
Or can you come stay with family?
是福曼
It's Foreman.
既然马克斯走了  应该停止了
Well, it should stop now that marcus left.
这才是主要的
That's the whole point.
对不起  是我的腿绊倒你了吗
Oh, I'm sorry. Was my leg sticking out?
最近我有点心烦
I'm so distracted lately, trying to think of something funnier
在想有什么比半夜爆消防栓更有趣
than fire sprinklers Going off in the middle of the night.
有什么提议吗
Any ideas?
不要激动啊老虎  我可知道你住在哪里
Whoa, easy there, tiger. I know where you live.
知道我怎么知道的吗
You know how I know?
因为那是我女朋友和我
'cause my girlfriend and I--
原来打算买的那个公寓
We tried to buy that very same condo.
为什么要把我算进去呢
Why don't you leave me out of this?
房子是威尔森买的
Wilson was the one who bought the place.
不过你住在那里
And you're living there.
你
You...
也要承担一样的责任
deserve to suffer equally.
因为刚才你绊倒了我所以我承担了更多
Actually, I suffered more now that you just tripped me.
他的抵消了
His suffering will equal out,
因为他很自责
'cause he actually feels remorse.
你为什么不直接说
Why would you out yourself?
你根本想不到怎么去报复
You can't even imagine the retribution.
不会再有了
Oh, there won't be any.
我已经停止了一切报复行动
I am ceasing all offensive operations.
我已经表明了我的想法  确立了优势
I have both made my point and established my superiority.
一旦你开始计划报复行动
And if you even get to the planning stages of retaliation,
我会告诉卡迪是你们两抢走了她梦想的房子
I will tell Cuddy that she lost her dream place to you two.
她很奇怪  一直认为你们是她的朋友
See, she's under this odd impression that you guys are her friends.
不是癌症
There's no cancer.
我们从头到脚的检查了一遍
We scanned him head to toe.
我们还做了白血病的检查
We checked blood smears for leukemia.
还有胸部超声波看他有没有乳腺癌
We even ultrasounded his chest looking for breast cancer.
可能我错了  关于他的体重下降
Maybe I was wrong about the weight loss.
你没有错  我们发现他的尿液袋里面有血
You weren't wrong-- we found blood in his catheter bag.
他的肾脏在衰竭
His kidneys are failing.
所以一定是癌症
so it has to be cancer.
只有肿瘤伴随综合症
Paraneoplastic syndrome is the only thing
会导致肾脏  心脏和肝的问题  还有暴怒
that can link kidney, heart, and liver-- even the rage.
为什么我们找不到它呢
Why can't we find it?
他的体内到处都检查过了
We've looked everywhere inside this guy.
如果不是在体内呢
What if it's not inside?
你知道为什么你那么黑吗
You know why you're black?
因为上帝爱我比爱你多吧
'cause god loves me more than he loves you?
我想说的是黑色素
Hmm. What I was going for was melanin.
你有太多黑色素了
You got lots of it.
使得你的皮肤很黑
It makes your skin dark,
保护你不受到有害紫外线的伤害
protects you from the sun's harmful U.V. Rays.
你在干吗
What are you doing?
不幸的是它也妨碍了那些有医疗证书的人
Unfortunately, it also prevents even those with advanced medical degrees
考虑恶性黑色素瘤的可能性
from considering melanoma as a diagnosis.
另一只手
Other hand.
黑人得皮肤癌的机率很小
On the rare occasion that black people do get skin cancer,
一般只会在白色皮肤的位置上
they usually get it on the white parts--
比如手掌和脚底
Palms and soles of the feet.
但因为打橄榄球  你的手脚磨损的很严重
But your hands and feet are so smashed up from football,
我的手下把你皮肤上的所有伤痕都当作淤青
My team are likely to have written off any skin blemish as a bruise.
但是目前我知道的
But now that I know that melanoma
只有黑素瘤符合一切症状
Is the only thing that fits...
过来看下这个  妈妈
Come take a look at this, mom.
豹爪上的一根小刺
There's the thorn in the panther's paw--
肿瘤伴随综合症
Paraneoplastic syndrome.
你的身体在集合抗体对抗肿瘤
Your body forms antibodies to fight the tumor.
那些微小的蛋白质
Those tiny little proteins
游离在你的血液里从而造成巨大的破坏
travel through your blood and wreak havoc.
我们移走这个痣癌
We remove the cancerous mole,
你就会好了
everything should be fine.
我会让奇斯医生安排手术
I'll tell Dr. Chase to schedule the surgery.
为什么要呢
Why bother?
我已经失去机会了
I missed my shot.
我的人生将会怎样呢
What kind of life am I gonna lead now?
你很认真很认真地学习了吗
Did you study really, really hard?
那你会和其他那些一起毕业的家伙们
Then the same crappy life that the rest of the guys
过着一样的废柴生活
You'll be graduating with are gonna lead...
除去学生贷款
minus the student loans.
你好了吗
Hey. You ready?
就快了
Almost.
恩  好了
And...done.
我听说豪斯和威尔森被人捉弄了
I heard house and Wilson are getting pranked by someone.
你完全不知情是吧
You wouldn't know anything about that, would you?
没有
No.
为什么我要相信你呢
Why should I believe you?
你说过我有张让人信任的脸
You said I had a trusting face.
我还是不明白
I still don't understand
为什么你不让我报复
why you wouldn't let me retaliate, though.
他们偷了你的梦想
They stole your dream.
太夸张了  那只是个公寓
Well, that's overstating it. It's just a condo.
不是因为你对整弄豪斯有愧疚感
It's not because you feel guilty about hurting House
也不是对和我在一起有愧疚感吧
or guilty for being with me?
我们可以买另外一个
We'll buy another one.
我只是觉得没必要为这个去争吵
I just don't see the need to make a war out of it.
恩  这很合理
Well, I think you're rationalizing,
任何一个没我有自信的男人
Which a less confident man than myself
都可能会把它当作事后教育
might take as a sign that you're second-guessing.
恩  忘了最后一句
Okay, you know what? Forget that last part.
我听说福曼和他哥哥
I heard foreman and his brother
和好了
are trying to work things out.
太好了
That's nice for them.
你能这样才是太好了
It's nice of you.
你没有挑动马克斯
You didn't provoke Marcus to quit
所以恶作剧将停止
So the pranks would stop.
你成了他们的联合公敌
You were becoming the common enemy they could bond over.
你就像是那些友善的玩偶的恶毒主人
You are the diabolical, yet benevolent puppet master.
我诱导马克斯辞职
I provoked Marcus to quit
是因为他已经没用
because he was no longer useful to me.
我雇他弄点消息
I hired him to get information.
他给了我要的消息
I got information. Uh-huh.
那我们怎么报复卢卡斯呢
And how are we gonna get back at Lucas?
没有报复
We're not.
我赢了
I win.